I don't need someone. Most women need
men. A lot of men need women. And that's
why they collapse. I've spent two years
with Jesus.
Because I know him. I now know myself.
You were pretty candid and you talked
about sexual purity being like a
struggle. You guys put it out there. Why
do you think it's so hard for young
Christians? You will never know how to
be in the will of God when you have
sexual sin in your life. You are so
confused. I thought I suffered so much
from obsessive and compulsive thinking.
I thought I was severely depressed. All
the things the doctor told me that I was
never going to get better. Tell me why
when I laid down my life and laid down
the sin, my mind is free. Who are y'all?
Y'all have the wisdom of 50-year-old
women. We are not meant to carry glory.
Only one person is meant to carry glory.
If this is what Christianity is about, I
don't want any part of it. I mean, I
have a little bit of a bone to pick with
some of the people because keep it real.
All right, I will.
This is the deep end with Lra.
Uh, I'm excited to be here today um for
a couple reasons. One is because
um I have some incredible guests who
have gone viral multiple times for
good things, for saying awesome things,
for saying things that are challenging
to the culture, especially um young
singles out here uh who love the Lord.
But also, I'm excited because um I have
a young daughter and um sometimes I'm
looking for content to give her to help
shape her perspective in her uh her her
growth with the Lord. And uh it's been
some of the content that these next
guests have created that have helped uh
my daughter process a lot of things. So,
I'm excited to have Ari and an here.
You know them as Girls Gone Bible. So,
uh, but yeah, thank y'all for being
here. Man, can we just say thank you for
that kind comment? I'm already
emotional. That was that was really kind
of you and we're so honored to be here
with you today. Absolutely. Absolutely.
Yeah. I I um
you know, it's it's it's difficult
raising
um daughters
as a as a man. I'm like, I don't know
what it means to be a woman. I don't
know what that looks like. you know, I
have a great wife. Um, but as the leader
and uh someone who's trying to like
shape my kids, so I'm always looking for
content, looking for things that just
appeal to their perspective. And um and
so you all were having a conversation
about modesty and um and I don't want to
police my daughter. I just want to
parent her, you know, and so present her
with various views and perspectives. And
I love y'all's conversation. And I was
like, "Oh,
listen to this. This is good." And she
did. And that wasn't the first or the
la. I mean, that was the first, but it
wasn't the last time. So, thank you,
Lra. That means the world. Like, you
shape culture with the content that you
make and your podcast and your music and
like we're just so blessed to even have
a conversation with you about Jesus,
about faith, about life, let alone
collaborate and do something together.
Like it really is such an honor.
Absolutely, man. I I love it. I love the
the thing I love about you both as well
is people would see you and even the
title Girls Gone Bible and think, "Oh,
perfect, pristine.
They, you know,
were raised in the church and like grew
up so perfectly and were choir girls at
seven years old." And that's not your
story. I wish it was. I wish.
So, so you guys were both pretty open
about what your lives look like before
Christ. Um I'm Can you like
walk me through your your stories a bit,
both of you? Yeah, of course. Um yeah,
so I grew up in I say I wish I don't
wish. I love my story. I love
redemption. I love what Jesus did and I
love what he does. Um, but sometimes you
hear something like your that and you're
like, h, there would be a lot less
scars. Like I would be fighting, you
know, maybe less of a battle or a
different battle at least. But so I grew
up in like my mom, my dad is of no
faith. He converted to Catholicism. He
was actually Muslim. He converted to
Catholicism to marry my mom. We're from
Albania. And so like her parents
wouldn't like absolutely give their
daughter to someone who wasn't Catholic.
He converts but has no faith for
himself. Um my mom is a diehard
Catholic. She loves Jesus and she loves
the Catholic church. And so I grew up
like in Catholic school um going to
Catholic mass every Sunday like and I
had a relationship with Jesus that was
like it was modeled after my mom's. My
mom's relationship with Jesus was very
much like because my mom's an immigrant
who's been through so much in her life
and so she has such a pure relationship
with the Lord. Um, and it's very like
survivalist based. Like it's very much
like you cry out to Jesus when you need
help. Like you pray and he comes and he
protects you. Um, and but I wouldn't say
that there was like a relational aspect
in the sense um there was no like fear
of God and there wasn't this element of
surrendering your life and giving
everything to Jesus and living for him,
obeying his commandments. like that was
never a topic of conversation in our
house. And so without that like deep
theological grounding, I was just like,
I love Jesus and nothing about my life
reflected my love for him, you know? And
so I fully lived in the world. I did as
the world did. Um I drank, I I partied,
I had boyfriends, I like I did
everything that the world does. And then
I found myself at 19. I was in college
in LA. I moved when I was 18 and I
started having like my mental health
started to go down so fast. I had one
panic attack that triggered chronic
panic attacks and I battled panic
disorder for almost 5 years like brutal
panic disorder. Like I mean I thought I
was losing my mind like fully gone. I
was like and it was only getting worse
because the fear in me just kept feeding
off of itself and it just kept growing
and growing. I had like phobias. I was
afraid of driving a car. I was afraid of
being on a balcony cuz I was like, "Am I
going to jump off? I don't know." Like,
I was just so full of fear. I had no
confidence. I was so insecure. I would
literally look in the mirror and be
like, "What is that?" Like, "Who are
you?" Like, I used to be this like
lively, confident, um, fearless girl.
And now I like can't even look people in
the eyes. I'm just full of fear. I'm a
shell of myself. Mhm. Did something
trigger the initial one or was it just
um you know I mean when I look at my
story there's so much pain in my family
story like substantial amounts of pain.
Um and a lot of Eastern Europeans or
immigrants in general they um they're
just in survival mode so much that there
is no context for like feelings or
emotions or anything like that. It's
just like chaos and you just want to
live another day. Gotcha. And so that's
how I live for so long. like you're so
tough, like you just take it on the
chin, you keep it pushing, you keep it
moving, and then like it caught up to
me, you know? You can't you can't run.
Yeah. And then so yeah, I I think I the
first day that I had a panic attack, I
remember nothing really triggered it.
Um, I was literally sitting watching a
TV show with my roommate at the time and
I just for the first time in my life
felt that panic feeling where like you
get tingles in your in your hands, your
body starts going numb, your legs are
numb, your vision starts to go and like
your heart starts beating out of your
chest and like everything gets hot and I
thought I was having a heart attack like
I didn't know. So I actually had my
friend take me to the hospital and so it
was so tre and they put me in a corner
in a chair and they were like you're
fine like you're just calm down but I
didn't know like I didn't know what it
was. There was no people weren't talking
about mental health as much back then
and so I would just then start having
them and I had a fear of having panic
attacks.
So I say all that to say I then started
self-medicating with alcohol cuz it was
the only thing that made me feel better.
Like it was the only thing that remotely
made me feel like myself. Like I wasn't
drinking to have fun. I was drinking
because I wanted to be okay. And that's
like what so many people do. Like
they're not even doing what they're
doing because they want to. They like
have to. And so yeah, start
self-medicating with alcohol. By 23 I'm
a full-blown alcoholic.
uh for six months. I like woke up at 8
o'clock in the morning and I had to have
a drink and it was so dark and it was so
devastating and scary and like you just
don't you just like don't recover from
that easily. Like I literally was like
I'm going to die. This is really bad.
Like I'm in a situation that like it's
over for me. And I was just a kid. Mhm.
And then um I met a man named Socrates
who's like my mentor. He changed my
whole life. He's like a spiritfilled
73-year-old man who is just like he's
just like so man of faith like word of
faith type. His name is really Socrates.
His name is Socrates. And he looks like
his name is Socrates. And he just he
prayed for me every single day for six
months over the phone. And he like the
first time I ever met him, he looked at
me and goes I was like probably drunk
like or not drunk but like drinking when
I went into his little studio and he was
like you are a mighty woman of faith and
you're going to tell millions of people
about Jesus and you're going to speak on
stages and you're going to write books
crazy. And then he just saw me like
Jesus saw me and he like just spoke life
over me. spoke, read scripture with me,
like just taught me about Jesus. And for
6 months that went on and then on
Thanksgiving 2019, I received what I
believe to be supernatural deliverance
after like full-blown alcoholic. Mhm.
Like couldn't go 30 minutes without
drinking or my body would start to shake
in a moment of complete like nothing
happened. Like it wasn't some big moment
where I cried out to Jesus. Like all of
those prayers, those six months led to
one moment
where like the stars aligned. Me and God
come into alignment. We come into
agreement that it's over. Mhm.
Coming on six years of being sober.
Never craved it one time. Hey, it's
unbelievable the crave. It's insane. I
love that. I love that. I'm there with
you. You're sober? Yeah. Absolutely. O
2018.
Wow. 2018 for any reason. Um I mean for
me I think it's understanding I went
through a dark season as well and
similar mental health struggles
self-medicating.
Um
but then a faith crisis as well. So I
was trying to really wrestle with like
God what's going on here? So, it was
kind of like alcohol became the the the
gateway to just a superficial piece, a
false savior. Uh but but yeah, I think
it was just it was kind of like some
people can toy with this, I cannot, you
know, this isn't something I can play
with. And same. Yeah. My father um was a
a drug addict as well, so I knew that,
you know, there was some some
generational stuff going on there as
well. So I' I'd leave it alone. Thank
you for sharing that. Yeah, absolutely.
So many people cuz it's such a
conversation, right? Like in my case,
it's like obviously you have to not
drink. Obviously you have to be sober.
But anybody, anybody, anybody, anybody
who you can tell you even remotely feel
like you're going to this thing for
comfort as opposed to Jesus, as opposed
to the real comforter, like there's
there's an issue, you know? Yeah. It's
super subtle, but yeah. And I appreciate
you sharing, too. Uh uh there's there's
so many similarities especially and a
lot of people don't understand panic
attacks, anxiety, and we're actually in
a an era in a generation where that is
increased way more because of social
media, because of so many other things.
But um for you to be transparent about
that is that's very great. Appreciate
that as well. Thank you. All right. So
give us your So but now that was her
story. But you were like I mean you were
raising youth group and uh and you know
Yeah. No, but you led worship. Yeah.
Yeah. You a worship leader at 12. No,
before Christ I was a Well, I grew up in
a small town in Massachusetts. Um I
didn't grow up in a household of faith.
Um before Christ, I was a girl who
suffered mentally. Um
I I come from generations of mental
illness. My mom really suffered. And so
that's what I thought was the norm. I
thought you have to take the medication
and you have to numb your brain because
that's the only way to be okay. Mh. And
so for me growing up watching her suffer
so much from her tormenting thoughts, I
just I thought the way I suffered was
going to be the way I would live my
whole life. Mhm. And I always um relate
my story to Mary Magdalene because the
way she suffered in her head with demons
just tormenting her mind. And I mean, I
suffered like that since I was just a
little girl. And I just always had this
desperation in my heart just to be
better. And I fought since I was a
little girl. I was always the parent. I
raised my sister. And then I just I just
always wanted more for my life. And so
I just fought my whole life. I moved
across country at 18. I was always
searching for for things to fill my
heart, to find peace, to find comfort,
to find some sort of safety. Mh. And so
I would do that in in relationships and
careers and I was just always coming up
empty. And I just kept my head down and
I just kept fighting because I had to
take care of my sister. I had to take
care of my family. And I didn't want to
be what I had to watch growing up. Like
my mom in the corner with her hands on
her head just suffering so much. Like I
wanted to be different, you know? And um
and I hit a wall in 2020.
My mind snapped
and I think I had been fighting for so
long. I went through such a bad
heartbreak. I lost everything. God had
stripped everything away from me and I I
I I believe I I was so tired from
fighting for so long since I was a
little girl and suppressing it. And um
my mind broke like I was I was dead.
Like my family said that I was I was
dead but somehow still breathing.
And um yeah, I would go to the doctor
and and I I just had this desperation
and I was like, "Help me." You know, and
they would give me these little pills
and it would just numb me out all day
and the sun would be shining and I'd be
looking out my window and it was just
all I could see was darkness, you know?
And I just was like, I can't believe I I
fought so long to be everything than
what I had to be growing up. And here I
am like just and I was done. I was like
so tired of fighting. And um yeah, God
had met me in the shower when I was
about to take my life and I had the the
water I'll never forget the day the
water was beating down on my face. I was
completely disassociated. My head had
hit the side of the floor and I had the
tormenting thoughts like worse than I
ever had in my whole life just telling
me to end it. how worth worthless I was.
And um it was just screams, repetitive
screams over and over.
And I had the pill bottle on the other
side of the shower and I was about to
take my life that day. Jesus Mhm. met me
in that in that shower. He lifted me out
of the pit and um I met him. I was I got
up and I I I didn't have strength for
for months. I couldn't even walk. I I
crawled to my shower and I got strength
and I got up and I put clothes on and I
started driving and it led me to this
little Catholic church by my house and I
went in and I laid in the pews and I
just cried out. I cried out for hours
and that safety and that love that I had
been yearning for since I was a little
girl was right there in that moment. M
and that's the day I met Jesus in the
shower and then in that church all in
the same day. God is truly near the
brokenhearted. Yeah, that's one of my
favorite. Me too. Life does not happen
bi-weekly. So watch your payday. The
money you earn can be in your hands
today with earn. Earnin is an app that
gives you access to your pay as you work
up to $150 per day with a max of $750
between paydays. So, just download the
earning app, verify your paycheck, then
access up to $150 a day as you work, and
leave an optional tip. Any money you
access plus tips are automatically
repaid from your next paycheck. So,
essentially, if you got to pay rent
really quick, it's the first of the
month, but you don't get your check till
the 5th, you can use earning to pay that
extra money you got to get paid, and
instead of a fee, just leave a tip. So,
there's all sorts of things that you may
be able to use this for. Maybe you need
that new dress immediately but you don't
have your check or you got an upcoming
event or you need a special night out or
it's date night and you haven't gotten
paid but you got to make it happen.
Well, earning can be a part of your
financial routine. You can join earn's 4
million customers who say things like,
"When I think about earning, I think
about financial stability, security. It
gives me a lot of peace of mind." So
download the Earning app today. It's E A
R N I N. It's in the Google Play or the
Apple App Store. And when you download
the Earning app, type in the deep end
with LCRA under podcast when you sign up
and it'll really help the show. Earn is
a financial technology company. It's not
a bank. Cash outs are based upon your
available earnings. Standard cash outs
take one to two business days with no
mandatory fees. an option to expedite
your transfer for a fee and tips are
voluntary and don't affect the service.
See the cash out user agreements for
details. Services are not available in
all states. Back to the podcast. Oh man.
Um,
so I I just got to say this because
there's so many ways I can I can go in
terms of talking about your story and
the podcast and everything that you have
going on. But I feel compelled to say
I know
in my heart and soul
that you all have liberated somebody
like this is this is freedom and I don't
think you understand
how
I mean you do understand because you
suffered in silence right but there's
someone suffering in silence who they
don't get to hear
voices like yours say the things that
you're saying. And when I say voices
like yours, I'm just being candid. Oh,
you both clearly went to Los Angeles to
pursue acting or modeling. You guys fit
the description of everything Hollywood
is looking for, everything the internet
says is perfect, right?
Um,
and then
you top on that. Oh, you and you love
Jesus, you know. Oh, perfect.
Everything's great. Like, it's great.
And people would look from the outside
looking in and say, man, they they got
it together. Mhm. And yet you sit here
and you talk about clinging on for dear
life, like saying, "If God, if I don't
even know where hope lies if you don't
rescue me." And that there's just a
level of vulnerability in that that sets
people free, that allows them to feel
like, "Oh, well shoot. If if if they can
struggle like that, then so can I." Mhm.
And if they can find freedom in that
struggle, then so can I. So I just want
to thank you. Thank you. Yeah. For that
liberation. Okay. Um it personally
connects with me because
I live through a lot of trauma, a lot of
mental health issues. My dad um
addiction and not being a part of my
life. my mom's side of the family having
severe mental health issues and and so
I would scour the internet because you
know I reached these heights and you win
these awards and you're on these
platforms but you're wrestling you're
struggling and you're trying to figure
out like why does everybody else look
like they have it together right but I
but I I'm breaking down inside and um
I'm just curious from you y'all's
perspective because I know you you both
came to LA to pursue like entertainment
careers. When you're What could you say
to
the young girls who are doing the same
thing you were doing and they're they're
entering into that space and they're
seeing all the lights, camera, action,
and they they're thinking, "Oh, this is
I'm just going to be a star and it's
going to be perfect and everything's
going to be amazing and there's not
going to be any problems." Like, what
would what do you say to them? Good. Um,
I mean, I would say so many things. I
would say so many things. I'd say first
of all, it's just so funny with
Christianity how sometimes like
Christian cliches can come off so corny,
but it's like they're the most true
statements ever. Like the lights, the
cameras, and the action will never
fulfill you. In fact, they only leave
you vulnerable and empty. And it's just
the truth. We are not meant to carry
glory. M only one person is meant to
carry glory. That's why all throughout
scripture you see you cast your crown,
you give the glory, all praise, all
honor, all glory to Jesus alone because
he knows that we are not capable to
carry. We were not designed to carry
glory. We are not actually not designed
to be stars. M we're not we're not like
the way like culture has li like they it
really has been so deceiving that we're
meant to go pursue the spotlight and
like yes coming from three people on a
podcast I know that can sound silly but
like Mhm. Yes, we are not supposed to
care. We are not supposed to have any
applause. We're not supposed to have any
glory. And so that's just what I would
say to anybody listening is that like
you really have to understand that what
you're searching for won't be found in
the things um that you're pursuing. And
and it is and it is true that like
especially girls going to LA and doing
these things. I totally understand it.
You have to protect yourself. You have
to be careful. It'll Hollywood will chew
you up, spit you out, use you, promise
you things that it never has any
intention of bringing you. Like, you
just have to be so unbelievably careful.
And if you're called to the arts, if
you're called to entertainment, if
you're called to acting, if you're
called to music, you just have to know
that you're called to it. Cuz people are
called. I have friends who are in the
acting industry who are on mission. I I
trust them. God trusts them in the field
because their hearts are not perfect,
but there's purity. Um, and they're and
they're trustworthy to be on mission in
these spaces. So, yeah, that that's what
I would say is like we're created and
designed to be on mission for Jesus. And
whether that's in the entertainment
industry or anywhere else, like you just
have to know that you're called there.
And then you have to do everything in
your power to make sure that like Jesus
is at the forefront of what you're
doing. And you have to have really good
people around you. You have to have
really godly people. You have to have
people who will tell you the things that
you don't want to hear. So good. God,
really good. That's so good. An there's
so much I could say with this. Um, you
know, when I was living in the world and
I because I lived in Hollywood since I
was 18, I would look around. And I would
be like, "Why is everyone so why is
everyone so depressed? Why are they full
of fear and anxiety? Why are they all
killing themselves? Everyone's
committing suicide. Why? They have
everything, right? They have the fame.
They're on TV. They got the money.
What's the problem? I had no idea. And
now I get it now that I have Jesus."
Fame is not real. It's never supposed to
be about yourself. And the minute you
look in at yourself, you've missed it.
And that's why everybody that is why the
light is coming to the darkness in
Hollywood because it's never about it's
never supposed to be about you. Yeah.
God doesn't sh God doesn't um God
doesn't share his his throne. And so
yeah, I think we have two we have we
have two things we have to do. We have
to know Jesus and then make him known.
And so everything we do and listen there
are times where we have to constantly
check our heart posture of course every
as human beings we're sinners we have to
check are we making it about ourselves
right now there's been many times that I
have but it's a constant daily check my
heart oh Lord search me give me a clean
heart because the moment we make it
about ourselves we've missed it you know
and so I just my motto is be as low to
the ground as possible. Yeah. Cuz the
lower you get, the more he decreases in
your life. And everything we do, we say,
"Is this going to glorify him?" Yeah. So
So you you all
on on the the you created this podcast,
Girls Gone Bible, right? And you guys
are in Hollywood and you're you've been
through it all. You've done the
auditions. You've seen all the chaos.
and
you're now pursuing Jesus. You're on
fire. You're passionate about him. Um,
you start this podcast because you were,
from what I understood, you weren't
seeing,
I guess, a version of you out there.
Yeah. Um, I guess like, you know, you
were trying to create a spaces for girls
who didn't fit the typical Christian
mold, so to speak. Um, and I guess you
know, uh, you've even articulated like I
I I didn't even feel Christian enough or
pure enough, you know, coming into this.
What What was that mold that you feel
like people that you were struggling
with and that other girls may be
struggling with to fit? Yeah,
I think I struggle with this more than
you. Or did you struggle with it?
Um, do you want to go for I just like
it's just so funny. There's nothing
more. How long have you had this
podcast? Uh, a year. A year? Oh, it's
like pretty new. Okay. Well, I don't
know about you've been doing this for a
lot longer than we have, I think. And
like it's just so funny even two years
ago. Just like you learn so much. You
grow so much. I was so underdeveloped
when we started the podcast that Yeah. I
had opinions then that like I look back
and I'm like that's so sweet, you know?
Um, do you want to go first because you
go ahead? Yeah. I just I think you know
back then I like I I was completely one.
I loved Jesus. Lroy my heart I would
literally everywhere I went I was like
telling everybody about Jesus. I wanted
everybody to be saved. I was a little
evangelist while fully living in the
world. M and like this is the part of my
story that I even struggle with because
scripture is so clear like if you love
me obey my commandments. How did I love
Jesus as as much as I did but but I
didn't obey his commandments. I didn't
do the things that he was calling me to
do or not do or just like living a life
set apart. And it just boils down to no
community, no accountability. Um I had
no fear of God because I didn't have
anybody around me that modeled that. I
came from a world that it's like you can
love Jesus and do whatever you want and
that's how most of at least the western
church lives. You know, it's cultural
Christianity and it's not inauthentic.
It's real. But you're deceived. You're
blind and you're prideful. And so I
start the podcast and and I'm I'm like,
there's nobody that looks like us. And
and now I look back and I'm like, well,
maybe that's good at that point. You
know what I mean? like she had there was
a lot of sanctification that had to take
place and like yes the church shouldn't
be judgmental but I just look back on
that version of myself and I I see that
she was just in process and I see that
like some things that maybe Christians
said to her were good for good for her
good you know so I just look back on
that version and yes I I love what the
Lord has done with Girls Gone Bible that
we did start out fully um in process us
being sanctified day by day. And you see
a master class of sanctification from
the inside out. From the words we speak
to the look in our eyes to the clothes
that we wear like our whole countenance
changes in two years. And it's like it's
incredible. It's genius of God to do
that. Um and I'm grateful that so many
girls and people saw us and said, "Hey,
I relate to these girls." Because they
didn't grow up in this world. But as
I've gone on, I've realized that like I
don't need to look like the world to be
relatable. I just have to share my
heart. And so we get into a really
tricky space where we think we then
there has to be mixture in order to
relate to people, but that's not
actually what they need. Yeah. Yeah. My
inadequacy came from self. Like I I came
from a different world. So I'm trying to
do this journey on my own. I'm going to
the church. This is new territory for
me. And I feel out of place. I feel
inadequate. I feel
I don't want to say I don't know if not
dirty, but I just felt like too far
gone. Like why am I even here? Like no
one's going to understand me from my
You're comparing yourself to other
people, too. Yeah. Everyone. And I just
felt like, yeah, I'm not No one's going
to get it. And so my inade my inadequacy
came from shame.
You know what I mean? It came from
shame, which wasn't real. Because at the
end of the day, I would go be the first
one at the front and I would ask people
for prayer and these beautiful Christian
people were putting their hands on my
head praying for healing. So, it's like
I know so many people think like
Christians and all this all this stuff.
But Christians, man, when we got some
good Christian community, they were
everything. They check up on us every
day. You can trust them. Mhm. So I just
a lot of people have church hurt. Yeah.
And I feel I feel bad for I feel bad. I
know I know people go through that. But
there are some beautiful Christians if
you get with the right people. Yeah.
Yeah. A lot of times people will I hear
people say like, "Yeah, these people
hurt me. That's why I don't go to church
anymore." And I and I and it's funny to
me because I'm like, I hear you and I
acknowledge your pain and I validate
your pain and what you went through is
is real.
However,
when I don't like a restaurant, I don't
stop eating the type of food that they
served me, right? I say, "This
restaurant didn't give me good
spaghetti." Doesn't mean I'm done with
spaghetti. Yeah. It means I may not eat
the spaghetti from this place, but that
does not eliminate spaghetti. And I
think when people say, "I'm done with
Christianity," I'm like, "Well, maybe
what you encountered was not authentic
Christianity." Maybe or maybe it was
broken people who were
misrepresentative, right? You know what
I mean? And so, but I I I like what you
said about both of you actually just you
were in process. Yeah. But sometimes
it's difficult to be in process in front
of the world, right? Oh, yeah. So, so as
you're doing this podcast and you're
getting eyeballs on you and you're
getting perspectives, there also comes
some level of scrutiny and there comes,
you know, slander and and different
things along those lines. How what are
what were the typical things you feel
like were coming up and how did you
process that? Yeah.
Um, I mean, early on in our journey, we
had so much stuff about modesty
and I'll just speak for myself in saying
like I love the people who said things
and write maybe I got comments that were
not necessarily nice and maybe people
should message you rather than
commenting publicly like sure all these
things. And I just I just think if you
like if you really do have a heart with
enough humility, like the Lord can
actually work through broken people to
reach you because even through like
yeah, it was just a level of
accountability that was um I think
actually good for me personally and
especially when I didn't have community.
Now that I have so much community, I
don't need to um focus on comments or
people online who I don't know. I can
look at the 10 people closest to me and
and receive their valuation. This woman
is wise. Y'all are y'all are wise. Thank
you so much. That's Anyway, go ahead.
Thank you. So, and and yeah, and I but
yeah, so I think we got stuff about
modesty. I think at the be in the
beginning we had a lot of rightfully so,
people didn't know if we were authentic.
They didn't know what this was about.
They didn't know if this was real. And I
just think over time I have to say like
we love Jesus so much. We love the Bible
so much. We both have hearts to teach.
We just want people to know Jesus. We
want people to be made disciples. Like
and I think that's come across. And so
we really don't get that much I mean.
Yeah. We don't I mean I have a little
bit
of a bone to pick with some of the
people because
it's hard because you you
keep it real. All right, I will.
I have some friends
that want to walk with the Lord, but
they look at some of the comments and
they're like, "If this is what
Christianity is about, I don't want any
part of it." M and we as people need to
do better. Mhm. Mhm. I know people that
have haven't been walking with the Lord
and just have integrity and are better
than these so-called Christians. Right.
Right. Right. And that's what I'm going
to say. Mhm. Um,
you know, it's just like the some of
these Christians call themselves
Christians, but they're putting like
faces under under photos and just it's
just so I just I will say that some of
the things that I've seen I can't quite
believe. I cannot quite believe what I
see in some of the comments, but they
call themselves Christians and they say
they've been walking with Jesus because
if you're really walking with Jesus, you
don't act like that. Mhm. Um, and I just
think that
I just think we need to do better. Mhm.
We need to be better. We need to check
our hearts more. Um, what I've seen
since walking in Christianity is quite
appalling if I'm going to be honest. Um,
so there's two sides to it. Um, but
yeah. Yeah, we've had to it's been crazy
growing in public. It's been like we had
to grow really really fast. It's it's
been a process, but man, it's been the
best thing of our lives laying down our
life so fast like that. It's been a
process and it's been hard and it's been
painful. It has coming from a totally
different world and having to shape up
in what four months we were like it's
it's been pretty painful. But thank you,
Jesus. Yeah. I I think community
is far more gracious than social media.
Yeah. Right. Like in community
there's a level of patience and
consistency and you know people aren't
going anywhere and you're going to see
them again tomorrow. So you don't say
just
crazy things to them because like this
person is a part of your community. Also
they love you. Right. Right. People
online it's just like yeah it's like
tough you know you don't even know if
these people are Christian. That's
what's you know what I mean? I there
have been so many times where I I've I
don't even know if I should say this,
but like I remember in the beginning I I
would be like looking at the comments
because they'd like destroy my heart.
I'd be like, "Oh my gosh, like I don't
know what I'm supposed to do." And I
would get a comment of like maybe a girl
like ripping me to shreds about modesty
stuff, right? I go and I look at the
profile, you click it, you look at the
profile picture and there it's like
wild, like no clothes and you're like,
"Wait, hang on. If you just click on
these profiles, you see it's not even
like you would never take this person's
opinion to heart, you know. Right. Well,
a lot of that what I find is what I find
is that they are
projecting. Yeah. Right. So, there's a
projection. Hey,
I'm not serious about Jesus
and I know I should be, but but you say
that you are. So, be better. So, good.
Be better than me. Yeah. you know, be
better than me. And wow. And then also a
lot of projecting of
what they think your motive is because
they know what their motive would be if
they were in your position. So it's
like, oh, you're just doing this to
whatever whatever. That's probably what
you would be doing, but that doesn't
mean that's what our motive is, you
know? So I that's a lot. I mean, I
guys are raised
just with this sense of beating each
other up for fun, you know? We we just
we kind of rip each other to shreds as
boys, so it's not as painful as we get
older, right? We're kind of almost used
to it. We're like, "Oh, shut up, big
head. Oh, your feet stink." Or, you
know, we just This is what we do. So,
it's not as like painful. But but girls
on the other hand, your tendency is to
just cheerlead each other in front of
each other and then behind you don't say
that stuff that you would really say.
You say it kind of behind their backs.
So I can't imagine young ladies having
to get flooded with so much criticism
that that's not how you're raised.
You're not used to just that's just not
how women interact. Like women aren't
kind of like, "What are those on your
feet?" You know, women guys never
compliment each other. Like rarely we
walk outside and some guy will be like,
"Okay, I see I see that shirt, brother.
I see I like that shirt on your back."
But you guys are like, "Oh, I love those
guys."
So, so I can't even imagine being a
woman and just like like dealing with
all of that. Um, but then on the flip
side, there's like
there's like this this this aesthetic of
Christianity on social media online that
is perfect and it is pretty and it is
put together and you know you you you
tend to dance I won't say dance but live
in between these two worlds. this one
world of like
you guys aren't,
you know, modest enough. You're not
saying the right things. This is not how
God would do it. And people think you're
not Christian enough.
Um,
you know, you're too edgy. But then
there's another side where you're too
Christian and it's like, "Oh, you guys
are so perfect and you guys have it all
together." Totally. Um,
what how do you process like are you
processing like am I being too
transparent? Am I being too vulnerable?
Am I being like am I sharing too much?
Because
you know there is a sense of like oh
Christianity online social media make
everything perfect. Jesus Jesus team
Jesus and everything's great. like how
do you process sharing the struggles,
the hard times, the the things that you
even though now that you know him, you
know, he he still suffered. Totally.
Right. So, how do you navigate that?
Um, yeah. I mean, Ari and I I think our
the beauty and how we've approached all
of this is that we just like let it all
out, baby. It's just like we don't know
how else to be. We don't know how else
to be. And that's just the truth. Like
we love it. The the beautiful thing
about I'll speak for both of us in this
is our spiritual formation. It not being
there's so much beauty and and value in
like finding a church right away being
in community. Um and then I and it's
really important and I will say because
of our spiritual formation where it was
literally first me just me and Socrates
and then just me and Ari and we didn't
really have anyone else. It does produce
like a very authentic
relationship with Jesus that's not based
in performance and it's not based in um
having to pretend to have it all
together because we've never had it all
together and we'll never have it all
together and we don't um have we're not
pastors kids. We've never had to uphold
an image. And so I think that's our
strength is that like this is all we've
ever known and like we're much better
now than we were in the past. So it's
like we're so every win with Jesus or
anything about Jesus, it's just like it
feels like victorious for us. So like we
love to share the struggles because this
is who Jesus is in it. It's never been
like you're a pastor's child and you
need to look the fit and like we've
never looked like we should be there. So
it's like, you know, do you agree? Yeah.
People are broken.
More suicides than ever. Yeah. M
depression's at an all-time high.
Infertility like it's you should see
what we sickness like you the stuff that
we hear and witness at our shows.
Is something I I I can't believe without
like with our own two eyes we are just
like wow. And so when we first did the
first episode I mean I always had a
facade online that I was perfect. You
would never thought. You would have
thought I was Princess Diana the way I
acted on Instagram.
And me coming out saying that I wanted I
almost took my life that I come from
generations of mental illness. I mean,
that was one of the hardest things I've
ever done. I was so exposed. The after
the first episode, I looked at her. I
said, "You need to get a new co-host. I
cannot do this. We're not releasing this
episode." like I and then we when we
finally did and we had a girl message us
saying because of your testimonies it
helped me stop taking my own life. And
so we looked at each other and we said
buckle up. And so that's what
testimonies do. They bear the image of
Jesus Christ.
And so just because we're on a podcast
that means nothing. We should all be
doing that. We should be doing that in
the back of an Uber. We should be doing
that in our jobs. We should be doing
that everywhere at Starbucks,
everywhere. That is our jobs. To be
open, to be vulnerable, to share our
testimonies. And you know, I do
understand what you're saying about that
other side of us where we're in our long
dresses with our bows in our hair and we
look, but man, we are just the farthest
thing from perfect. And um yeah, we
struggle and every day it's a constant.
We work through things. We we struggle
every day. Oh, we work through things.
We we we every day.
Yeah. Sorry. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So,
that's good. So good. I love y'all's
transparency, too. Like, it's it's so
refreshing, honestly, because
I I mean,
by you could be biased and look at you
online and look at your thumbnails and
just kind of like
there's not going to be transparency
here. This is going to be perfect. and
pristine and then you get rocked with
not just transparency but truth. It's
like, "Oh, they take the Bible seriously
and like, oh man, Jesus is this is
great." Like, and I I think that's a
it's a powerful testimony. I feel like
you flipped
Satan's agenda on its head because the
agenda I think the enemy would have had
for you is to just be aesthetically
pleasing,
be entertaining,
and and say the right things and you'll
go far. Yeah. And instead, you're you're
saying, "No, I'm going to die. I'm going
to deny self. I'm going to" And I think
that's that's powerful. Um Thank you.
Yeah. one one of the as we're speaking
about denying self um about a year or so
ago, you guys did an episode where you
you you were pretty candid and you
talked about sexual purity being like a
struggle and um I think that was like
that was like wow you you guys put it
out there. Um, I think it probably set a
lot of people free, but I'm but I'm
curious like
Yeah. Like why do you think it's so hard
for young Christians from y'all's
vantage point in this era? And then like
how did you all end up slaying the giant
and putting it down? There you go.
Sin is one of the most passionate things
we like to talk about because it truly
set us free. It brought us from darkness
to light. I didn't fully go into the
light until I laid down my life of sin.
Mhm. Um it took me a minute because my
pride told me I've been living this way
in my relationship since I was, you
know, 17. Um and so to come to the world
to to come from the world and then and
then basically I came from the world,
met Jesus, started the podcast, laid
down my life. It was like boom boom
boom. And it was jarring at first, but
it truly I thought I had all these
mental problems. I thought I suffered so
much from obsessive and compulsive
thinking. I thought I was severely
depressed. All the things the doctor
told me that I was never going to get
better. Tell me why when I laid down my
life and laid down the sin, my mind is
free. I don't have tormenting thoughts.
Obsessive compulsive thinking. who
when I laid down the sin, I was free.
I'm not in bondage anymore. Do you know
what I mean? And that wasn't by my own
strength. That was Jesus when I fully
got down on my hands and knees. I'll
never forget the day. And I had to get
some good Christian community. I looked
up. I said, "I need your help."
I'm done. Yeah. You know, I'm on the
podcast. I'm in my Bible. I'm praying.
But there was that one thing that I
didn't lay down. And why did I have no
peace?
I had no peace. I still had chaos in my
belly and in my mind. And so I knew sin
was staring at me in my face. And as
Christians, we when when we know Jesus
and we know his word, we cannot have one
foot in and one foot out. You can and
and we just talked about this with
Philillip. You cannot be walking with
the Lord but be living in habitual sin.
Yeah. You know, some things we do in
ignorance, but when we know better, we
do better. God doesn't make us have all
these rules. He does it out of his love.
And because we love him, we want to obey
his commandments. And so when I truly
decided to follow him, that's when I was
set free. Yeah. No, I I'll never forget
I think I was
I was a little fresh out of college and
um wasn't married,
but um you know, my current wife and I
weren't weren't together.
Um I was kind of dating around a little
bit and um I was a campus minister, like
a campus leader. And I remember I had to
do a show for like a YMCA, you know, I
was just getting started. And
the night before the show, the girl I
was dating and I
were being intimate. Mhm. And um I'll
never forget waking up the next morning
just feeling like
like I was like I I want to die. Yeah.
You know what I mean? Now, there's
conviction, but then there's also
I didn't even realize I had fragile
mental health. So, I'm piling on
shame and guilt and the conviction of
the spirit onto a fragile mind. That's
right. And it was it was it was
torturous. It was torturous. I hated
every minute of it. And it was kind of
like, but I think to your point, people
are playing with that on a regular basis
and not even realizing that's one of the
ways Satan keeps you in bondage is it's
how it can keep your mouth closed from
being a voice for the Lord because
you're living in shame and bondage and
you're like, I can't say anything cuz I
Yeah. what I did last night. And so, and
there's something about sexual sin, like
we know obviously scripture talks about
how it's the one sin that you commit
against your own body. And like all sin
is created is equal in God's eyes. But
there's something about sexual sin
specifically that it being against your
own body, it perverts your mind in a way
that no other sin does. When you talk
about sin opening up like doors to the
demonic, nothing like sexual sin. You
cannot see clearly. If you're engaging
in sexual sin, you cannot see Jesus
clearly. There's grace because he loves
us and he's long-suffering and he's
patient. He was patient with me. I
remember when I was still not walking in
purity. And this is when we had first
had the first couple of months on the
podcast. I was in a relationship and I
had this journal that I still have and I
wish I had it to read because it's like
insane. I would literally write. I would
I was coming to Jesus in despair.
Writing to him saying, "Jesus, I'm dead.
I am spiritually dead. I am just getting
by. I have nothing in me. I don't know
what's going on. I don't feel you're
nowhere to be found. I know you're here,
but I have separated myself from you."
And I was just dead. I was dead in the
sin. My peace was dead. My joy was dead.
You will never understand. You will
never know how to be in the will of God
when you have sexual sin in your life.
You are so confused. Period. Period.
Yes, there's grace and there's the
sovereign hand of God that will he works
and that's what he does. He's so good to
us that he will still work in your life.
But you with your own vision, if g if
the pure in heart will see God, Jesus
must be your greatest vision. To have
any sort of direction in life, that
can't happen when you have sexual sin in
your life. And I remember one of the
most significant moments of my life.
This is I have like a handful of like
really profound encounters with Jesus.
But I Ari and I were in Texas and we met
with some girls who I wrote about this
in the book. this moment where I'm like
confronted with these two Christian
girls who are dear friends of ours who
are modest and they're pure and they
just like they just do it right and I'm
like confronted with like wow this is
everything that I'm not like it was so
confronting for me and then for the next
couple of weeks and I'm in a
relationship like I'm I'm I'm extremely
convicted but I don't know what to do. I
don't know where to start. I don't know
how to stop. Like I have no idea who am
I without this? Who am I without being
promiscuous? Who am I without dressing
like this? I've been conditioned my
entire life to look a certain way, act a
certain way, get validation from
something very specific. Who am I if I
have to let this go? Mhm. And I had this
moment where I like I got home from
something and I went into my bathroom
and I was looking at myself in the
mirror and I don't get visions that
often, but I felt like the Lord took me
back to seeing myself as a little girl
when I was in this house in Connecticut
and I saw this really really young
version of myself and she was so free
and she was so innocent and she was just
like running around and I felt God in my
heart be like you can have this
innocence back. I heard it so clearly in
my heart and I'm just like
and then like so much shame came up and
so much guilt and so much good godly
grief of just being like man I've I've
done it wrong for so long and it feels
like time missed and time wasted and
like I just I felt like I you know hurt
Jesus so badly but I just felt this deep
sweet calling gentle like just come just
come to me. Mm-m. Just come. And yeah,
I'll never forget that day. I literally
called my boyfriend right after and I
was like, hey, I was like, I can't. It
had already been in conversation, right?
But like there had to be I needed Holy
Spirit empowerment. Like I needed
something to shift. Yeah. And in that
moment, I called him. I was like, I I
I'm done. I can't do this anymore.
Luckily, he was like, all right, let's
do this. We didn't date for very much
longer. Um, not for any reason other
than it just wasn't my husband, but like
yeah, it was so it was insane. It was
really really profound. That's that's
Yeah, that's liberating. I mean, you
again, I just I I know there's people
watching and listening to you all and
like it's liberating. his chains falling
off because sometimes scripture says we
overcome by the blood of the lamb and
the power of our testimonies and you are
so testimonial and just testifying to
the work that Jesus has done through you
and you're not ashamed like I just
imagine like
the prostitutes who are following Jesus
like like oh I'm not ashamed no I'm not
ashamed yep that was me and but this is
the new me and I love that about you all
like I I'm claiming a different
innocence. I'm a new creation, a new
creature. I love that. Um,
you said something.
You said boyfriend.
Um, I know you've talked about
singleness a lot on your podcast.
Apparently, your singleness journey is
ending.
Um, I guess you're still walking in
singleness. Yeah. Um, I have a lot of
questions about this. First question is,
what is life like dating in the LA
streets?
We talked a little bit beforehand, but I
mean you guys were You want to go first?
Please go first. I mean, I don't really
know what that we date in the LA
streets. I don't think we ever have. We
don't go outside. Okay. So, how do
people how how did how did
the people that you engaged or that
engaged you, how did they find you?
Yeah. I mean, I actually right before
Jesus, of course, dating in LA
is
it's not LA's fault. Like, it's not LA's
fault. It's just, you know,
places in which they're spiritually
depraved at times, you know, like I
can't even talk about my life before
Jesus because it was just like, you
know, like who knows what you're doing
when you don't have Jesus in your life?
None of us. Chaos, you know, makes no
sense. Chaos. There's no like you don't
know up from down. Mhm. Um when I
started following Jesus, I probably had
or like really started to give my life
to Jesus, I was um dating. And yeah, I
guess for me once I actually started
living in purity. That's where like I
feel like my life began. Like I didn't
date. It doesn't count. Like it doesn't
count. You know, you weren't trying to
follow the Lord with relationships. You
were just like, "Yeah." And so until I
started pursuing purity, I actually had
eyes that could see what matters and
like what I value. And like for me, this
I'm telling you, I mean, in my walk with
Jesus, it was important for me even
before I was walking in purity that I
would have a man of God who prays and
who's like spiritually gifted. Like that
mattered to me so much. After I started
pursuing purity, then my whole life
opened and I said, I literally don't
care what they look like. I literally
don't care what they do for a job. Like
I need to know who they are in Christ.
Like that's truly and like you can
testify that's like literally all I
cared about. Um is someone I wanted
someone who could pray for me, who could
go to bat for me. And so dating in LA, I
guess, um, in any sort of environment
that is focused on self, where men or
women are focused on self, it's it's
going to be incredibly difficult to find
people with the same values as you. I
always say, I think the best thing you
can do is tell the godliest people in
your life that you're looking and have
them find someone for you. Come on. You
know, and have it be like a word of
mouth thing. I like that. Yeah. That's
how I met my boyfriend who's like or
your dad if he loves Jesus.
Um yeah. And so my boyfriend, he's like
his name is John. Um he's he's an angel
and we met through word of mouth. We met
through we basically got set up on like
a blind date. He's from a sweet sweet
town in Idaho and he's just perfect. And
so you know like so dating in LA I don't
know. I don't know how to Well, I've
heard it's really rough. N so you're not
dating in LA. you you're just Yeah. I
No, not not yet. I I had to go on a
journey with Jesus, just me and him. I
had to go on a journey of um purity. And
I had to go on a journey of not putting
my identity into another person. I went
through a horrendous breakup. I was with
the person for almost four years. And so
I I wanted to heal with Jesus. I didn't
want to keep putting a band-aid over a
wound. I wanted to heal it. Mh. And
thank God I did. And it's it's taken me
a little longer than I thought. But I
just said this in the last episode, I
can wake up in peace. And I love myself
and I'm comfortable with myself now. And
I never thought I could be this woman
that I am. And it happened later in life
for me. Yeah. Um, I think the hard thing
about dating is in the Christian world
is that everybody gets married really
young. And so, um, yeah, I think that's
the only thing. But, but Jesus, I know
he's got someone so special for me. I
have so much faith. Yeah. But yeah, I've
been in this waiting season. I think now
I'm I'm I'm ready. Yeah. Now I'm ready.
Yeah. But I don't know about LA, man. I
don't know. And I have to say if I can,
Ari's like it's profound just the way
that she has truly like
actually taken like singleness as a gift
and like you have I feel like you have
to like choose to make it a gift. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. You have to choose to make
it a blessing. You have to choose to not
look at it as a curse. And like I just
like I just have to honor her in the
fact that like she really doesn't like
feed off of male attention. She doesn't
look for validation. And like she goes
to the source. Mhm. She goes to the
source. And it's like I I I just I wish
I had her to look up to when I was
younger so I could have been like,
"Okay, that's what you do when you're
waiting." It's really special. I mean,
Paul said he he wishes everybody would
stay single like him. So, I think
singleness gets a bad rap. I think in
the Christian space, we kind of like
look like if you're single, like like
poor you instead of like what an
incredible opportunity to serve the Lord
and to do things that couples can't do.
Exactly. You know, if I if I just want
to take off and go to Tanzania to go
serve. I got to make sure my wife is
good, my kids are good. How's this
going? But as a single guy, I'm out of
here. I know. You know, so the way I've
been able to do the Lord's work through
my singleness, only through my
singleness, the places I've gotten to go
to, the friends I've made, it's just me
and him. It's so special. There's
something so special with just being
with him. So the people you pour into
Yeah. My my philosophy is
marriage is hard, single is hard, choose
your heart. That's it. That's what it
is. Yeah. Yeah. Just choose your heart.
Marriage is a blessing. Singleness is a
blessing. Choose your blessing. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. You know what I mean? So,
that's how I that's my my perspective.
Um, what what do you think are the
common pitfalls? Because I've heard you
there couple things I've heard you all
say. one, I heard you say, "Man, I I I
want to
just sit and stare at a man who is
further along than me in my faith
journey and be led
in this modern
kind of uh feminist
space that we exist in." I could see
people being like, "Oh, be led." Um, so
I thought that was admirable.
uh for you to say, "Man, I just want
someone who" because that's the marriage
that I'm in. My wife is like, she has no
problem being like, "No, you're the
leader." And being a leader means I'm
not a tyrant. It means I lead in
humility. I lead in service. I lead in
listening. You know what I mean? You
lead in preferring your wife. Exactly.
So, it's like that's part of leadership.
But um but I've heard I've heard that
and then I've also heard
um you know you you both talk about some
of the the pitfalls of women trying to
find their worth in men. What do you
what do you think are the struggles
right now that y'all are seeing for
young women in looking for men?
Yeah.
The number one is I'm gonna go back to
what I just said. Putting your identity
into a person. If you are if you put
your identity into another person,
you're always going to be coming up
empty. And that's why I am so glad I've
spent two years with Jesus.
Because I know him. I now know myself.
And whoever comes into my life will just
be added. I don't need someone. Most
women need men. A lot of men need women
and that's why they collapse.
The other thing I'll say is for worth
for validation. Worth for validation. I
need you. Identity. Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's good. And the only place
you can find your identity is through
Jesus. Yeah. Um and then the other one
I'll just say is we have this checkbox
list. Me, I was one of them. But as I g
get older, I'm realizing,
you know, we all want the tall and the
handsome or the beautiful or the one
with a lot of followers, but what about
the person who can hold you up when your
faith falls? Who's going to be by your
hospital bed if God forbid something
happens to me? s if God forbid something
happens to you. Who's going to make the
phone call if God forbid something
happens happens to one of your family
members and they have to make some big
decisions? So that's where I'm at right
now. I want the guy who's going to help
my dad if he falls, who's going to help
me, who's going to put their hands on me
and pray for me if God forbid something
happens where I lose my faith. Like this
is what we need to be looking for. But
the problem is is everything is so just
dis like disposable now. Swipe less. Oh,
she's not. Whatever. I'll move on. They
think the grass is always greener. And
it's not. It's not. Who are y'all? Y'all
have the wisdom of 50-year-old women.
That's crazy. It's so true. It's so
good. True. It's so true. Yeah. It's so
true. What was your question again?
Sorry.
No, just like what? Okay, that's what I
wanted to make sure. Yeah, I think for
women, just to piggy back on what Ari
was saying, you find a man
who is captivated by Jesus. Cuz I'll
tell you one thing, everybody's a little
annoying.
Anyone who's married will probably
Everybody's a little annoying. Everybody
Yeah. every I know I'll be annoying one
day. Everyone everyone is going to
bother you. Everyone is going to make
mistakes. Everyone but like a man or a
woman who is it's it comes down to the
will. If your will is broken and your
spirit yields to God and you have
humility in your heart and a willingness
to say I'm sorry and let me be better
that if if anybody who is governed by
the spirit of God not anybody because
everybody is imperfect but like if
somebody is captivated by Jesus I'm
telling you look no further. I'm not
saying that attraction isn't important.
Mhm. It is important. You do. I I
believe that God wants you to be
captivated by and attracted to the
person that you're with, but like it
just goes so much so much deeper than
that. So if we could encourage people
for anything with anything um it's to
find someone who's so captivated by
Jesus because they will
make mistakes but you can you can you
can have faith that they're going the
right direction. You can have faith that
you get into a fight and they're going
into their room and they're consulting
with God and seeing how to move forward.
I just like I can't even imagine and I'm
not saying that like missionary dating
doesn't ever work. We we've seen it. But
we know it does, but it's so few and far
between. And I just I that should not be
the standard. You know, the standard
should be following somebody who wants
or to date someone and marry someone who
wants to look like Jesus. And so, yeah,
I think for girls, um, they're
struggling being led. I think men are
struggling to lead. I think that we're
on the come up because more, you know,
right now more than ever, men are going
to church. the number I don't know the
statistic but um it's gone up by a lot
where more men are in church than women
at the moment and like yeah we just need
we need to teach our sons to lead and as
women we need to empower men to lead we
need to speak to them as if they're
already the leaders that we want them to
be you know we need to speak life over
them we need to give them confidence we
need to like give them space and this is
coming from somebody who like I don't
need a guy to do I got it like you know
what I mean I it is a work of the spirit
that allow that like is able to break
off that independence and actually give
your man your person the space to come
and be the leader that God intended them
to be. That's really good. It's really
good. Yeah, you guys you guys are
exuding wisdom. It you it would it would
you sound like preachers kids or like
I'm a good pastor like
like a godly good dad pastor but it's
really good. God has really developed
y'all well. Um
my personal belief I I I think that
politics has become a very divisive
issue specifically within the church. I
think that um
historically you could you could go cast
your vote and still love Jesus on both
sides of the aisle. I do think there's
believers on both sides of the aisle who
love Jesus. I've had two people in here
at the same time who had a civic
conversation. It was beautiful. They
discussed their differences, their their
views. They loved each other and I
thought it modeled something. Um but in
2025 it's a divisive issue specifically
in the church. Um
I I saw your you all prayed at the the
pre-inauguration. How and I'm I'm the
the divisiveness came up like what are
they doing there?
How how do you navigate that? How do you
pro process what's going on in that in
that time period? Amen. Um,
all I'll say is is is
yeah, we got a lot of lot of heat for
that. But if we get the chance to pray,
we're going to pray for our nation. And
we would do it for either party.
If we get the chance to pray in the back
of a cab, we'll pray in the back of the
cab. If we get the chance to pray on
stage for the president and for our
nation, we're going to do that. And it
came with a lot of prayer. And we did
that. And we had peace.
And when we have peace, we know it's God
saying, "Go." Yeah. And so we are at
peace with it. And um we're happy we did
it. Yeah. We're happy we did it. Yeah.
Yeah.
You know, I only have one problem and
it's that we didn't bring close it out
with leading people to salvation. I
know. That's that's the only thing I
anywhere we can go to preach the gospel
and talk like I don't care. like you can
I don't care where it is like I any we
want to preach the gospel. We want to
preach the gospel. And my only thing is
I should have said um if you're in this
room just say these words. We didn't
know what to expect. Yeah. And and you
know what was beautiful about that whole
thing is that like we had the liberty to
do whatever we wanted. We could have
said whatever. We for me personally like
I wrote out my prayer route and then I'm
like I send it in and like it has to get
approved. And I was like, "Oh, for sure
they're not going to let me say all
this." Like, "For sure they're not going
to let me pray this." And they let us go
for like eight minutes. Like it was like
it was insane. And there was no
adjustments, no corrections, no. Can you
water it down? So I'm like, "If they're
going to allow" And I remember saying
like, "If this prayer, this is this is I
sat with the Lord and this is what I
believe the Holy Spirit is telling me to
pray. If this doesn't get approved, like
I'm not going." That was a deal that I
had where like it was just a little it
was confirmation.
And when it came back I was like this is
amazing. Like this is like a literal not
watered down version of the gospel
whatsoever on a massive stage like this.
Like it's so it was so cool. And yeah,
there's a political spirit that is like
it's wild how divisive it is and it's
terrifying and it rocked us for a second
like I think that's the last political
thing we'll be doing. Yeah, I think we
might not. I think we're good. Like
we'll pray in private. We'll we'll let
you go and pray in private for now on.
No, no. I've I've dealt with the same
thing. You know, it does it doesn't
matter. It's kind of like there's an
expectation of Christians on one side of
the aisle that say if you show up to
something on either side of the aisle,
you're not really representing Jesus.
And it's kind of like we're not trying
I'm kingdom over empire but I will
always pray
you know God's will in the empire. So
I'm sure Daniel I'm sure there were
Jewish people who were like are you
really going to help King Nab? You going
to help this man? He just destroyed our
city. Don't give him advice. Right.
Right, right, right. I think what gets
me through with, you know, just like the
divisive political stuff is like I
always think about Jesus
rides in Palm Sunday. He's on a donkey.
Everybody thinks that Jesus, the
Messiah, the savior of the world, the
king of the world, is going to come in
on a horse and chariot. And sweet,
humble, lowly Jesus rides in on a
donkey. Not coming to overthrow the
Roman Empire, but he's coming to
overthrow sin. Like that's who Jesus is.
We cannot get it twisted. Like you
search the scriptures and you see who he
was. He never reached for any sort of
political power. And like Yeah, that's
just that's my take on everything.
That's how we all need to be. Yeah,
that's great. Servants. They're
screaming hosana. And that was like they
were thinking it was it was a political
chance. They're like, "Yes." Yeah. He's
like, "Hate to disappoint y'all."
Hate to disappoint y'all. Hey, listen. I
hope you guys enjoyed this episode of
The Deep End. This episode is brought to
you by the Amazing Life Foundation, and
I've worked with this team for over a
year now. They've helped me produce this
show since the beginning. Amazing Life's
mission is to help people grow and
flourish through high quality content.
and I just want to thank them for making
this show possible. Now, back to the
podcast. Um,
let's talk about the book, you guys. So,
you you you do the Girls Gone Bible
podcast, you do the tours, and now
you've got this book. Um, talk to us.
What's the book about? What's it called?
What are you hoping to see happen? Go
ahead, please. Please. Sorry. This is
what we do. She said, "Go ahead. Please
do. We fight every time I go. refer to
you. No, no, no. No. The first will be
last, the last will be first. You go
first. No. I I'm being humbled. No.
Being lowly. Get us out of the
wilderness. So, it's called Out of the
Wilderness. 31 devotions to walk with
God through your wilderness season. Um,
and it's just one of the greatest
privileges, honors of our lives is like
two girls who if you would have told us
we'd write a book, we would have been
like, "What are you what? What are you
talking about? We can barely read." I
look at her, I go, "We can't even read."
like it's it was just the most beautiful
um opportunity to like really go through
our whole lives, our whole walks with
Jesus and pinpoint every moment so many
different moments where we felt we were
in the wilderness where we felt like
being in the wilderness is like when you
don't know where God is. You can't hear
his voice. you feel like you're
wandering and you're alone and you're
just looking out into the abyss going
where are you? And then I think the
beautiful thing about the devotional is
it's like we are in those moments 31
days where we're in those moments both
of us we alternate from day to day. And
um and it seems like God is nowhere to
be found. You don't see his hand on it.
You don't know where he is. And then we
we tell the story and then we let you
know where Jesus was in it. And a lot of
it is speaking in hindsight, you know,
like you don't always know in the
wilderness where he is. So I think for
us it was just an opportunity to give
people hope in whatever wilderness
they're in to understand like we have
history with God. And like if you don't
have history God, you can read our
devotional and you can glean off of our
history with God because history with
God is like that's the hope that we have
um in the wilderness when you don't know
where he is. And so we just love like
it's it's hope through these pages. It's
like God's hand in different moments in
our lives where we thought it was the
end. We thought that it was really bad.
Mistakes that we've made like and and
like purity, modesty, alcoholism, broken
hearts, eating disorders, like the
either the mistakes that we've made or
the tragedy that happened to us and
where Jesus is in it and the redemptive
arc of the gospel in our lives and how
Yeah. and how we we wouldn't be who we
are without those wilderness seasons.
Mhm. And how anything in the hands of
God, it's never wasted. And as I even
read through those pages, I'm like, all
those moments where I was like, why is
this happening to me? Why did I have to
go through that? I would never be where
I am right now. She would never be where
she is right now. He uses the pain, the
brokenness, the addiction, the abuse as
a child, the mental illness of
generations. It's like he uses it for
his glory. And so it just you read it
and you're like, I'm not too far gone.
Yeah. Like there is hope. That's so
good. Like this wilderness does have a
purpose. Because it does. And because of
our wilderness, because of our
wilderness season, we can look in the
eyes of others and say, "Me, too." How
glorious is that? So yeah, wilderness
seasons are the it's they're hard in the
moment, but they've been the greatest
blessing for us. Yeah. And to write
about it, it just like I I just think
for people to have um something on paper
and like what matters to us, like we
built this on the word of God and like
it's just the most important thing to us
ever. Like we don't ever ever ever ever
want to stray away from the word and we
never will. M um and so yeah, every it's
just full of scripture. It's full of
different Bible stories. Every day has a
different um you know, part of scripture
that I think is so beneficial for
people. That's so good. Yeah. I
I want to make sure people go like get
your devotional. I'll make sure my
daughter's going to get one of those as
well. Um I guess what what I would my
encouragement to you both
um just after being
behind the scenes in this Christian
space for so many years
is that
just please continue to keep your
strength as your weakness. Yeah. Right.
Like your your strength is your
weakness. Um,
there's just going to be so many
opportunities for you to acquies and
just kind of like
fit into the mold that I I won't say
Christianity, I'll say the the Christian
industry, you know, cuz there's there's
two different things. There's biblical
Christianity and then there's what like
this
this industrial complex where we sell
Jesus to people through these these
models and and we we got to go through
those pipelines a lot of times that's
you got to go through it to sell your
book or to get your pot all those things
right you got to touch it but you don't
have to pretend
that you're strong
and I that's the most powerful thing
about y'all to
you you just come here and your your
boast is in Jesus. It's I mean you guys
are brilliant. You're transparent.
I mean you guys are beautiful young
ladies but you're not relying on that
and that is that's the strength. So
please keep that up. So kind. Yeah. That
is so kind. I can't thank you enough for
that. I love it. It's It's encouraging
to me, man. Um, y'all blessed me. I
really appreciate. Um, listen, you
blessed us. You're so gifted. Can I be
honest? I was taking notes the whole
time cuz you are so good at interview.
We're not interviewers. We like I took
notes the whole time. I was like, I'm
going to watch this back and be like,
"All right, so he like you're just so
It's just so good. You go and it was the
most natural conversation." I and I'm
being serious like sometimes you on
podcast there is no bit of performance
in this room. There's no self in this
room. There's no like not even just with
you but like just with us too. I feel do
you feel that we're Are you It has been
one of the greatest honors to sit across
from you. Oh man. The definition of
pure, man. And I mean that the way how
kind you were to us. Yeah. You are an
incredible man of God and we are honored
to sit across from you today. Thank you
so much. Listen, I've been around a
while. I have seen some things. And can
you tell us?
No, but I just I when I see this level
of purity and passion, I I just like,
"Oh, keep that. Please keep that." Cuz
this place will try to drain it out of
you, you know? And you know, if God
can't make you bad, he'll make you busy.
And so you'll just be so busy that you
just,
you know, you're not focused. Oh my
gosh, I don't like that. I mean, the
devil, if the devil can't make you bad,
he'll make you busy. I didn't mean God.
God God won't make you bad or busy.
Lord, forgive me, Lord. Uh, but if the
devil can't make you bad, he'll make you
busy. And I just kind of like But I love
the Y'all y'all have a I Yeah, I don't
know. I haven't seen anything like y'all
in generations, so it's just refreshing.
You know what I mean? It's like, oh,
this is refreshing. It's like, huh, I
wonder what Beth Moore was like when she
was this age or something like, you know
what I'm saying? So, it's dope. It's
just dope to see. Just I I love it.
Thank you. Can you come on GGB?
Absolutely. You promise? Absolutely. I
would love that. Okay. I would love
that. We would love to have you on. When
are y'all back in LA next week? Yeah,
next week. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Uh
um you and Dera come out a lot. Yeah,
we'll be there. We'll be there next
week. We're going to San Diego, too.
We'll be there next week. So, so we talk
about relate leaving. We do have you
both on and we
Good luck. And really, good luck. She's
so like that's okay. I'm so Oh my god.
What am I going to say? I don't know
what to say. I don't know what to say.
That's how I feel sometimes, too. What
am I going to say? She's full of wisdom,
though. Of course. But just when the
camera's on, she's like, I don't blame
her. It's like it's the it's so hard.
Look at us. Okay, first of all, I
literally look what I'm wearing. I'm so
upset. She goes, I look like a chef. I
look like a I look like I'm supposed to
wear the hibachi hat. Like, I'm like,
talk about I know I didn't try on
whatever. I didn't try on the shirt
before I bought it. Can you keep this in
there so they know I don't So they know
I don't think I look good. Okay, good.
Thank you, Jesus. Thank you. Listen,
listen. No, true story.
I was at uh I my wife got a flat tire
last night, so I woke up. I usually have
a pretty rigid schedule. Wake up early,
go to the gym, leave a gym, then I get
in here, um you know, do my my have my
time, podcast, go to the studio. It's
usually what happens. My wife got a flat
tire last night. She was concerned. I
said, "Just don't worry about it. I'll
take your car and get the tire swapped
out this morning." So,
you know, I skip my whole routine. I
drop her car off and I'm like, they're
like, "How long will it take?" I said,
"About an hour." I said, "Cool. I'll
just get my steps in and do like a hour
little walk around this this complex." I
get back, car, the tire's still not
fixed. So, I'm like, "Man, I got to
catch an Uber to get over here." I left
my clothes in the car. So, I'm just
like, "Well, all right. This is what
this is what we're doing. Well, I mean,
that makes me feel better. I'm like,
this is what we doing today. All right.
This is what we doing today.
So, it's fine. You You're good. Thank
you. Okay. You're great. Thank you.
Anyway, um but no, man, I appreciate.
This is really good. It's way
like I didn't have I I expected to be
good, but it was like beyond my
expectations. You really feel that way?
Yeah, I did. I've seen the podcast. I've
seen what you guys talk about. It's
trying to be about to be itself, but No,
no, you guys keep it so real. It's
refreshing. First of all, I wouldn't
have put my daughter in front of your
stuff if it wasn't. Amen. Thank you,
Jesus. That can that is the greatest
compliment anyone could say. Oh, yeah.
The way that we feel the responsibility.
It's just like every word that come like
I Yeah. We have so much conviction of
what comes out of our mouths at all
times just because yeah, there's just so
much weight to it. Well, she knows even
the most sincere and godly Christians
get it wrong sometimes because she lives
with me.
So, I love that. That makes us feel
better, too.
Yeah. Um, but yeah, man. Thank y'all so
much. Um, thank you so much.
This is the deep end with LRAY.